mycity.com 2018-08-23

# Privacy Policy - MyCity

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy: Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use Edge Up Network & Mycity.com after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices. 

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about: 

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by Edge Up Network & Mycity.com
  * How the information is used.
  * With whom the information may be shared.
  * How you can access and change your Account information.
  * What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by Edge Up Network & Mycity.com.
  * How to contact us.

### Information Collection

#### Registration:

In order to become an Edge Up Network & Mycity.com user, you must first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to login using your email or Facebook account. Once logged in, Edge Up Network & Mycity.com will capture your name, email address, country, region (Metro Area), and current company name and any other information that you input during the signup process. Edge Up Network & Mycity.com will also request that you manually provide a brief summary of your company (i.e. a 'pitch'), and a few ways to describe yourself and/or your business (industry types, skill sets, and more). 

####  Profile Information: 

Once a user, you may provide additional information to your account including various ways people may contact you including phone, Google+, Skype and more.. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better promote your business and find new opportunities within Edge Up Network & Mycity.com. 

### Information about your Contacts

In order to invite others to connect with you directly on Edge Up Network & Mycity.com, you will enter their names and email addresses (we also provide a contact upload form for bulk invites). This information will be used by Edge Up Network & Mycity.com to send your invitation to connect on Edge Up Network & Mycity.com.

You may also choose to manually enter or upload data about your contact. All information entered will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com network without your permission.

All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own personally identifiable information.

We store this information (including phone numbers) and use it to help you manage and leverage your contacts in connection with our services.

We also use this information to enhance your experience: identifying your leads that are already connections via LinkedIn, other social platforms or within email communication.

When you send an email to another individual on Edge Up Network & Mycity.com or to join Edge Up Network & Mycity.com, that person may have access to your email address or, for SMS invitations, mobile number because it may be displayed in the communication.

After sending these invitations, we may also remind your invitees of your invitation on your behalf. Your leads may also have access to your email address. We make other tools available to sync information with Edge Up Network & Mycity.com, and may also develop additional features that allow users to use their account in conjunction with other third-party services.

For example, our mobile application allow you to sync your email and/or contacts with Edge Up Network & Mycity.com.

Another example are software tools that allow you to see our and other public information about the people you email or meet with and leverage our services to help you gain insights and help you prospect new leads.

If you grant Edge Up Network & Mycity.com permission to access your email, they will access and may store some of your email information. Our products that sync with external email services may also temporarily cache message content for performance reasons, in a way that is unreadable by us and our service providers.

Any information that you upload or sync with our Services is covered by the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. You can remove your information at your convenience by going to your accounts page or sending an email to bob@edgeupnetwork.com. 

You can remove your address book and any other synced information at any time. 

### Cookies & Log Files

Like most web sites, Edge Up Network & Mycity.com uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Edge Up Network & Mycity.com to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you've logged in to your Edge Up Network & Mycity.com account. The next time you visit the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to login before using the service. In order to access or change any of your private information (like a credit card number), however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Additionally, if you log out of the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com site you will need to re-enter your login credentials the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com sites. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Edge Up Network & Mycity.com. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law. 

### Web Beacons

We may allow other companies (although not presently), called ad networks, to serve advertisements to Opportunity users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. Edge Up Network & Mycity.com may “target” some ads to users that fit a certain general profile - for example, “web designers looking for accountants in Tampa, FL.” These ads may also be promoted within emails sent to each user. To deliver these ads properly, O Edge Up Network & Mycity.com may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by Edge Up Network & Mycity.com so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other websites.

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network's servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other websites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. You will never see additional ads as a result of being an Edge Up Network & Mycity.com user and Edge Up Network & Mycity.com never provides personally identifiable information to any advertiser nor any third party.

### Children

Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service. 

### Information Use

Edge Up Network & Mycity.com is a lead generation tool designed to bring professionals together in a more intelligent way. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself and your company to others. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by Edge Up Network & Mycity.com from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by Edge Up Network & Mycity.com. This information can be utilized by Edge Up Network & Mycity.com at its sole discretion. 

### EdgeUpNetwork& Mycity.com Communications

Edge Up Network & Mycity.com may communicate with you through email, direct mail, telephone, mobile phone, IM, desktop and mobile notifications and text messages (SMS). These may include a series of promotional and informative emails regarding new features and services provided by Edge Up Network & Mycity.com as well as notifications to alert you of new business Edge Up Network & Mycity.com with other members. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Edge Up Network & Mycity.com related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user requests to connect with you. Edge Up Network & Mycity.com may send you promotional information at any time. 

### Customized Content

Information you provide at registration or in your Profile section is also used to customize your experience on the website and app. For example, when you login to your account we may partial information about you and your company on our homepage when people log-in. The intent (obviously) is to provide you with immediate and maximum exposure Edge Up Network & Mycity.com.

Additionally, many users upload third-party logos to their profiles. Edge Up Network & Mycity.com neither endorses nor is affiliated with most of these third-party companies. In most cases, Edge Up Network & Mycity.com is not affiliated with these companies. If a company feels the logo placed on a profile is in violation of their trademark guidelines, they should contact the profile owner and/or contact Edge Up Network & Mycity.com directly to have the logo removed.

### Sharing Information With Third Parties

Edge Up Network & Mycity.com takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will only share your personally identifiable with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. For instance, we use a credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

Edge Up Network & Mycity.com offers a “public profile” as well as Search Engine Optimization (SEO) features which publish portions of user's profiles, including “name” and “company name”, to the public Internet. Users are given the chance to opt-out of this SEO feature through their Account Settings. Edge Up Network & Mycity.com will also share portions of your contact information (no email or phone) with other members who we have determined to be a good match. The spirit of our website is to connect people more intelligently and efficiently. Simply put, if you do not wish to have your contact information shared with other users, you should not sign-up for Edge Up Network & Mycity.com.

We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by role (i.e. product managers, vice presidents), industry, geographic location, company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users' activities on the site, please email customer service. 

### Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services

Edge Up Network & Mycity.com may partner with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services it will be your choice to make use of the combined services or not. 

### Communications Between Users

Many emails you initiate through Edge Up Network & Mycity.com an invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will list your name in the header of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about you and your company. Other communications that you initiate through Edge Up Network & Mycity.com, like a request for contact, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. However, your contact information will be shared with another user if both of you have been determined by Edge Up Network & Mycity.com to be a “match”. At which time, an email alert will be sent originating from Edge Up Network & Mycity.comy containing various ways in which the user can communicate with you including email, phone, Skype and more. 

Edge Up Network & Mycity.com provides the User with a platform on which to establish contact with other users, and only provides those technical applications that allow users to contact one another. With regards to content, Edge Up Network & Mycity.com does not take part in any communication between users. If users enter into agreements with one another over the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com website, Edge Up Network & Mycity.com shall not be a contracting party to these agreements. The users alone are responsible for the execution and/or fulfillment of agreements in which they enter with one another. Edge Up Network & Mycity.com shall not be held liable if users are unable to contact one another over Edge Up Network & Mycity.com websites regarding such agreements. Furthermore, Edge Up Network & Mycity.com shall not be liable for breaches of duty in relation to agreements entered into between users. 

### Point and Rating System

Edge Up Network & Mycity.com uses a verification / rating system (both public and private) to understand our users AND provide the overall community with an understanding of the quality of the users on the network. You may be awarded credits/badges based upon your status within the system (PRO Member, etc ...) and/or your use of the system. Edge Up Network & Mycity.com may adjust your credit balance or rating, change system credit values or modify the credit and rating system at any time at its discretion. Credits have no monetary value and are not redeemable. 

### Legal Disclaimer:

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

### Accessing and Changing Your Account Information

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your Edge Up Network & Mycity.com account, at any time by editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account through the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com website. If you close your Edge Up Network & Mycity.com account, We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the Edge Up Network & Mycity.com service, please send your request to bob#@edgeupnetwork.com Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with Edge Up Network & Mycity.com under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to bob@edgeupnetwork.com usually within a few days of the receipt of the email. 

### Security

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data (including credit card information) on Edge Up Network & Mycity.com is password-protected. At the present time, we do not have access to any detailed credit card information (unless provided directly over the telephone or at one of our events), as that is hosted entirely through our third party merchant service provider. 

### Subscriptions

#### iOS

Get your monthly PRO subscription through the app starting at $4.99 (prices may vary depending on country and currently active offers). When you subscribe, you will be charged a price according to your country and the subscription you choose. The price will be shown in the app before you complete the payment. The subscription renews every month (or year) unless auto-renew is turned off at least 24 hours before end of the current subscription period. Your iTunes account will automatically be charged within 24 hours prior to the end of the current period and you will be charged for one month (or year) at a time. You can turn off auto-renew at any time from your iTunes account settings.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Edge Up Network & Mycity.com may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

### Questions or Comments

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at bob@edgeupnetwork.com or contact us at:  
Edge Up Network & Mycity.com  
Attn: Privacy Policy Issues  
17412 Ventura Blvd, Suite 24  
Encino, Ca 91316
